[Music]
It was the night of 15 July and it was hot
An act of treason burned the country
Today today the whole nation stood up
Children and children, old and young, took to the streets.
Democracy was hit by a coup, people were shocked
Either freedom after this, or humiliation
The footsteps of millions made the place tremble
Flag in hand, takbir in tongue, ran forward
We are the witnesses in the epic of democracy
We are the martyrs who die one death and rise a thousand
The commander-in-chief gave the order: Get in the square!
Protect the flag, the beloved homeland!
We gave up, for the sake of homeland, nation and God!
The whole world was shocked to see this!
[Music]
From the ground, from the sky, while those traitors are dying
Many lives fell martyr while raising the flag
Some defied the tank, some defied the gun
So that democracy is never again
Democracy has suffered a blow, thank God nation
Either freedom after this, or humiliation
The footsteps of millions made the place tremble
Flag in hand, takbir in tongue ran forward
We are the witnesses in the epic of democracy
We are the martyrs who die one death and rise a thousand
Commander-in-Chief gave the order; Get to the square!
Protect the flag, the beloved homeland!
For the sake of homeland, nation and God!
The whole world was shocked to see this!
[Music] Clap, clap, clap... He'He'Hey!
I wish our 251 martyrs mercy from Allah and condolences to their places. Subtitle: EmirKaptan Admini